[
{"question": "Which cricket team has won the 2017 Vijay Hazare Trophy?", 
"options": ["A. Karnataka", "B. Gujarat", "C. Jharkhand", "D. Tamil Nadu"], "answer": "D. Tamil Nadu"}
, {"question": "Who was the first Indian in independent India to have won a medal in an individual Olympic event ?", 
"options": ["A. Dhyanchand", "B. K D Jadhav", "C. Prithipal Singh", "D. Harishchandra Birajdar"], "answer": "B. K D Jadhav"}
, {"question": "What does the Olympic Flame symbolize?", 
"options": ["A. Zeal to play sports", "B. Challenge", "C. Continuity", "D. Integrity"], "answer": "C. Continuity"}
, {"question": "Consider the following:
Badminton
Bowling
Golf
Table Tennis
The sporting event “Singapore Open” is related to which among the above?", 
"options": ["A. Only 1", "B. 1&2", "C. 1,2&3", "D. 1,2,3&4"], "answer": "D. 1,2,3&4"}
, {"question": "Which among the following is the women’s equivalent of the Davis Cup?", 
"options": ["A. Hopman Cup", "B. Fed Cup", "C. BMW Open", "D. Millrose Cup"], "answer": "B. Fed Cup"}
, {"question": "The terms Volley, Smash, Service are related to which among the following sports?", 
"options": ["A. Volleyball", "B. Lawn Tennis", "C. Table Tennis", "D. Badminton"], "answer": "B. Lawn Tennis"}
, {"question": "Sandy storm” is the autobiography of which among the following veteran cricketers?", 
"options": ["A. Dilip Vengsarkar", "B. Mohinder Amarnath", "C. Sandeep Patil", "D. Roger Binny"], "answer": "C. Sandeep Patil"}
, {"question": "The name of S Vijayalakshmi is famous in which among the following games / sports?", 
"options": ["A. Badminton", "B. Table Tennis", "C. Chess", "D. Hockey"], "answer": "C. Chess"}
, {"question": "The famous football player Maradona belongs to which among the following countries?", 
"options": ["A. Brazil", "B. Chile", "C. Argentina", "D. Italy"], "answer": "C. Argentina"}
, {"question": "“Electra Gold Cup” is associated with which sports?", 
"options": ["A. Lawn Tennis", "B. Table Tennis", "C. Badminton", "D. Football"], "answer": "B. Table Tennis"}
, {"question": "The Commonwealth Games started from which among the following countries?", 
"options": ["A. England", "B. Australia", "C. Canada", "D. India"], "answer": "C. Canada"}
, {"question": "Omega Mission Hills World Cup is related to which game?", 
"options": ["A. Tennis", "B. Golf", "C. Hockey", "D. Polo"], "answer": "B. Golf"}
, {"question": "The term “Tee” is used commonly in which among the following sports?", 
"options": ["A. Tennis", "B. Polo", "C. Golf", "D. Racing"], "answer": "C. Golf"}
, {"question": "Ryder cup is related to which sports?", 
"options": ["A. Polo", "B. Golf", "C. Tennis", "D. Lawn Tennis"], "answer": "B. Golf"}
, {"question": "Who among the following has written the book “Cricket My Style”?", 
"options": ["A. Sunil Gavaskar", "B. Anil Kumble", "C. Kapil Dev", "D. None of them"], "answer": "C. Kapil Dev"}
, {"question": "Which among the following tides (as they are called) from the surf and winds?", 
"options": ["A. Storm Tides", "B. Rip tides", "C. Neap tides", "D. Tsunami"], "answer": "B. Rip tides"}
, {"question": "Which among the following is the National Sports of USA?", 
"options": ["A. Bowling", "B. Baseball", "C. Table Tennis", "D. Rugby"], "answer": "B. Baseball"}
, {"question": "Who among the following is the First Indian Women to get an Olympic Medal?", 
"options": ["A. Anju Bobby George", "B. Karnam Malleshwari", "C. P T Usha", "D. Nameirakpam Kunjarani"], "answer": "B. Karnam Malleshwari"}
, {"question": "Euro Cup is related to which sports?", 
"options": ["A. Badminton", "B. Football", "C. Table Tennis", "D. Hockey"], "answer": "B. Football"}
, {"question": "", 
"options": ["A. ", "B. ", "C. ", "D. "], "answer": ""}
]